Guide to the Arleen Schloss Papers MSS.437
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Performances and Exhibitions, 1960-2013; 82.4 Linear Feet in 44 cassette boxes, 33 record cartons, 12 manuscript boxes, 5 LP boxes, 5 flat files, and 4 flat boxes; 665 audiocassettes; 202 Hi8; 170 VHS; 137 MiniDV; 78 U-matic; 58 Quarter_Inch_Audio_Reel; 29 Half_Inch_Video_Reel; 4 Betamax
  - Subseries I.C: Events by Date, 1967-2013
    - Layered tape made at Ernie's, July, 1989; cuid44168 (Box 151, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0018)
    - "Land Mines: An Exhibition of Outdoor Art and Sculpture," 2B, August 5 - October 15, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - "China: An Exhibition," Asian American Arts Centre, October 12 - November 19, 1989
      - Ephemera (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Video (Box 94, Hi8 437_1407)
    - SADATO "Dill", December, 1989 (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0929)
    - Christa, 1989 (Box 91, Hi8 437_1298)
    - Christa, Buster's show, Joshua's performance, Connie, 1989 (Box 97, Hi8 437_1962)
    - Project for James Lund, 1989-1990
      - Audio, 1989 (Box 83, Audiocassette 437_0759)
      - "Homeland Suite," G. Kajfez and G. Arevalo, 1989 (Box 82, Audiocassette 437_0727)
      - "Above Water", July, 1990 (Box 90, Hi8 437_1271)
    - Hanja, Berlin, circa 1989-1990 (Box 124, Vhs 437_1404)
    - Art Sparks, circa 1990s
      - No. 1, June 29, 1991 (Box 91, Hi8 437_1284)
      - No. 2, undated (Box 99, Hi8 437_2032)
      - No. 3, Lynne, undated (Box 98, Hi8 437_2001)
    - Live Sculpture -- Example of projection, light movements, circa 1990s (Box 130, Vhs 437_1626)
    - Merce Cunningham Pseudo, circa 1990s (Box 137, Vhs 437_1781)
    - Rivington School, circa 1990s
      - 50th anniversary, Tomiyo, 1991 (Box 99, Hi8 437_2031)
      - Asian Art Center, Toyo, undated (Box 106, Minidv 437_2338)
      - Beginning of Rivington School, undated (Box 152, 16mm film reels 437_2420)
      - Rik Little and The Church of Shooting Yourself, undated (Box 130, Vhs 437_1642)
    - Tekno Time, circa 1990s (Box 144, Vhs 437_2153)
    - Audio Arts Festival, June, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 7, Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
    - Xanacus, Roundtable #1, Awards with demos and speeches, September 13, 1990 (Box 103, Hi8 437_2195)
    - Socrates Park, end of Met, October 28, 1990 (Box 136, Vhs 437_1767)
    - Steel Wheels, Stones live, Winter, 1990 (Box 66, Audiocassette 437_0064)
    - Do Do Ya Sa'Si So -- Anna Homler, 1990 (Box 74, Audiocassette 437_0382)
    - Arista's Rock Sampler -- "Sex, Lies and Audiotape", 1990 (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0355)
    - Bernie (Dub), 1990 (Box 106, Minidv 437_2309)
    - Fashion, 1990 (Box 136, Vhs 437_1763)
    - In New York after A.E., 1990 (Box 100, Hi8 437_2035)
    - The Met, Petri Court, 1990 (Box 134, U-matic 437_1823)
    - Langing in New York, George Chakiris, Nik, 1990-1991 (Box 97, Hi8 437_1963)
    - Rainbow Installation by Ray Kelly, 1990 - 1996 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Dumpster and bust, Holly's dance, January 21, 1991 (Box 90, Hi8 437_1269)
    - A at Minolta, A on Wall St, Land T fashion show, Buster Diane, March, 1991 (Box 99, Hi8 437_2012)
    - The Kitchen at Town Hall, May 6, 1991 (Box 91, Hi8 437_1304)
    - Lauren Basmitsvah, May 11, 1991 (Box 100, Hi8 437_2051)
    - Art World Bronzes, May 21, 1991 (Box 99, Hi8 437_2010)
    - Michael Holman -- "(plea) / dream," Tompkins Square Park, June 7, 1991 - March 1992 (Box 99, Hi8 437_2022)
    - Urban Harvest Fest, Charlie Morrow, Parade, September 21, 1991 (Box 98, Hi8 437_1985)
      Label also reads "Nik's Camera"
    - Alan Waters Lecture, Wetlands, September 29, 1991 (Box 98, Hi8 437_1993)
    - "Burp," Kitchen, October 24-25, 1991
      - Video, October 24, 1991 (Box 98, Hi8 437_1998)
      - Video, October 24-25, 1991 (Box 92, Hi8 437_1322)
        Music by Michael Pugliese
    - Tom Kaye, October 31, 1991 (Box 91, Hi8 437_1307)
    - The Drawing Center, the Great Hall, November 10, 1991
      - Part one (Box 143, Vhs 437_1933)
      - Part two (Box 143, Vhs 437_1932)
    - Bar Talk, 1991 (Box 102, Hi8 437_2176)
    - "Chance and Chaos", 1991 (Box 75, Audiocassette 437_0460)
    - Richard Kostelanetz, Kaddish, 1991 (Box 114, Vhs 437_1039)
    - Susanne Wibroe -- Riptide at Socrates, 1991 (Box 139, U-matic 437_1890)
    - Zatar -- Party Frankenstein, 1991 (Box 157, Audiocassette 437_0146)
    - "In this mouth and computer," Arleen piano, 1991-1992 (Box 102, Hi8 437_2103)
    - Kung Yu Fong, March 31, 1992 (Box 100, Hi8 437_2036)
    - Rob Lane, May 8, 1992 (Box 90, Hi8 437_1273)
    - Our new Kwok, August 8, 1992 (Box 94, Hi8 437_1383)
    - Joanie, Stux, Tompkins Square, circa Fall 1992 (Box 97, Hi8 437_1964)
    - Exodus, September 4, 1992
      - Bronx, New York (Box 141, Vhs 437_1920)
      - Jeff Wistotsky (Box 93, Hi8 437_1351)
    - Kwok, September 15, 1992 (Box 99, Hi8 437_2026)
    - Harvestworks Benefit, October 8, 1992
      - Part one (Box 92, Hi8 437_1329)
      - Part two (Box 98, Hi8 437_1988)
    - Masako and Nells, October 21, 1992 (Box 99, Hi8 437_2006)
    - David Boyle #2, November 6, 1992 (Box 99, Hi8 437_2017)
    - Phil Kline and Carol, December 20, 1992
      - Video (Box 100, Hi8 437_2038)
      - Video (Box 136, Vhs 437_1766)
    - Compilation Tape -- Construction, Performance Rehearsal, Gallery Portraits, A Day in the Life of PS 19, 1992 (Box 88, Minidv 437_0986)
      Exterior label reads: "Construction on Broome St.; Nik watches TV; Performance rehearsal, G. Lewis; street steam; gallery; Empire St. WTC; across Broome st.; TV 1992; gallery photo portraits; a day in the life of PS19; TV news, fades; Crista; kid's birthday"
    - John Cage Performance (Early Edit), Xi'an, 1992 (Box 117, U-matic 437_1097)
    - Masako, 1992 (Box 92, Hi8 437_1310)
    - Masako Fashion, 1992 (Box 114, Vhs 437_1056)
    - Monkey King Peking Opera Performance, 1992
      - Ephemera (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Video (Box 142, U-matic 437_2116)
      - Video (Audio Source from Loft) (Box 142, U-matic 437_2114)
      - Video (Box 88, Minidv 437_0976)
      - Video (Audio Source from Loft) (Box 88, Minidv 437_0977)
    - Piano, Brian Ferry, October 10, 1992-1993 (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0924)
    - Moon Pulse Screening at A's, circa 1992 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - "The Wisdom of the King," David Boyle, 1992-1993
      - #3, November 7, 1992 (Box 101, Hi8 437_2080)
      - Video, April 30, 1993 (Box 92, Hi8 437_1328)
      - Video, May 1, 1993 (Box 90, Hi8 437_1254)
    - Tom Luckey, May 16, 1993
      - Audio, PCM (Box 94, Hi8 437_1386)
      - Video (Master) (Box 99, Hi8 437_2028)
      - Video (Dub) (Box 124, Vhs 437_1579)
      - #1 (Box 101, Hi8 437_2087)
      - #2 (Box 93, Hi8 437_1361)
      - #3 (Box 99, Hi8 437_2027)
      - #4 (Box 100, Hi8 437_2034)
    - Anna Tucker and Arleen, jazz, January, 1993 (Box 81, Audiocassette 437_0700)
    - Buster Cleveland, January 23, 1993 (Box 96, Minidv 437_1476)
    - Talk with Hedda Sterne, Opening at Philippe Briet, January 23-28, 1993 (Box 101, Hi8 437_2081)
    - Buster Cleveland, January 29, 1993 (Box 96, Minidv 437_1487)
    - Philippe Briet Gallery, February 5, 1993 (Box 100, Hi8 437_2052)
    - Joanie Sanding, March, 1993 (Box 90, Hi8 437_1253)
    - St. Patrick's Day, Artists, March 17, 1993 (Box 92, Hi8 437_1316)
    - Stelarc, March 19, 1993 (Box 99, Hi8 437_2018)
    - Dennis Ashbaugh Opening Reception, Marisa Del Re Gallery, March 25, 1993 (Box 98, Hi8 437_1973)
    - John Wheeler, May - June, 1993 (Box 100, Hi8 437_2033)
    - Leroy Jenkins, Felicia Morton, June 20, 1993 (Box 99, Hi8 437_2021)
    - "Political Art Documentation and Distribution: The Padd Archives" Exhibition, MoMA, June 1993 - May 1994 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Loop Art, Connie's, 1993 (Box 66, Audiocassette 437_0068)
    - Tobey and group talk, Arleen exhibit, January, 1994 (Box 124, Vhs 437_1580)
    - Jam session, Stadtische Galerie im Buntentor, January 24, 1994 (Box 94, Hi8 437_1370)
    - Exhibition Butties Henry, Tapeh 8 Galerie, February 3-5, 1994 (Box 100, Hi8 437_2050)
    - Last tape of exhibit, Bremen, February 5-6, 1994 (Box 102, Hi8 437_2104)
    - Americans for Equality, March 12, 1994 (Box 98, Hi8 437_1979)
    - Jack and Mikee, April - June, 1994
      - Basketball, St. Marks Bar and Grill, April 10 - June 5, 1994 (Box 98, Hi8 437_1974)
      - St. Marks Bar and Grill #2, Ken, May 1-8, 1994 (Box 101, Hi8 437_2088)
    - Ringlingbos -- Edit Master, May 11, 1994 (Box 114, Vhs 437_1033)
    - Rudolph Grey, May 28, 1994 (Box 93, Hi8 437_1355)
    - "Box in a Valise," Museum of Modern Art, June 22, 1994
      - Luca Memorium (Box 101, Hi8 437_2072)
      - Proposal (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Video (Box 143, Vhs 437_1936)
      - Video (Box 93, Hi8 437_1350)
    - Pang Hy Sung, Lincoln Center, August, 1994 (Box 98, Hi8 437_1980)
    - Kwok at Tweed Gallery, June - September, 1994
      - Video, May 9, 1994 (Box 102, Hi8 437_2177)
      - Video, June 9, 1994 (Box 99, Hi8 437_2020)
      - Arleen presentation, taped by Kwok's friend, September, 1994 (Box 135, Vhs 437_1722)
    - Marjorie Kouns, September 14, 1994 (Box 93, Hi8 437_1348)
    - Arleen and Nam June Paik's homage to Charlotte Mormon, Washington Square Park, October 8, 1994
      - Nam June Paik, Washington Square, FA_MSS_437_ER_14
      - Video (Box 96, Minidv 437_1535)
      - Video (Box 67, Hi8 437_0104)
      - Video (Duplicate) (Box 93, Hi8 437_1365)
    - "Frog King" Installation and Exhibition by Kwok Mang Ho, November 12 - 18, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Stadtische Gallery in Buntentor, Bremen, November 16, 1994 (Box 100, Hi8 437_2039)
    - Linus, Marbles, December, 1994 (Box 94, Hi8 437_1373)
    - National Art Club, December 5, 1994 (Box 101, Hi8 437_2067)
    - Excerpts from Bremen, Stadtische Galerie, 1994 (Box 136, Vhs 437_1757)
    - Filmklasse Music Evening, by Joachim M. Neumann, 1994 (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0932)
    - Fluxus, 1994
      - Nam June Paik's Performance (Box 136, Vhs 437_1771)
      - A and Nik (Box 130, Vhs 437_1636)
      - Ben Patternon (Box 100, Hi8 437_2049)
      - Meiko, Shegeko, and Jean Dupuis Performances (Box 99, Hi8 437_2019)
      - Video (Box 120, Vhs 437_1214)
      - Video -- Part one (Box 157, Minidv 437_1489)
      - Video -- Part two (Box 157, Minidv 437_1490)
    - Grateful Dead, 1994 (Box 97, Hi8 437_1970)
    - "History of Works" Exhibition, 1994
      - Marika Heinz Hooke Opening (Box 144, Vhs 437_2156)
      - Rough edit (Box 136, Vhs 437_1773)
    - Knitting Factory with Tom Buchen, 1994 (Box 114, Vhs 437_1052)
    - Mingfay -- Master Edit, 1994 (Box 136, Vhs 437_1769)
    - Newband, January, 1994 (Box 131, Vhs 437_1698)
    - Palm Shore Club, 1994
      - Sarah, Coco, Nik, Penelope (Box 97, Hi8 437_1967)
      - Video (Box 134, U-matic 437_1822)
      - Video (Box 94, Hi8 437_1387)
      - Video (Box 92, Hi8 437_1337)
    - "Schloss mit Hochschule," Städtische Galerie, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Electronic Sculpture with Movement, 1994-1995
      - Video (Box 137, Vhs 437_1798)
      - Video (Box 143, Vhs 437_1938)
    - Merkin Concert Hall, January 19, 1995 (Box 115, Vhs 437_1062)
    - Jana Haimsohn, February, 1995 (Box 93, Hi8 437_1345)
    - "Interpretations," Thomas Buckner, Merkin Concert Hall, February 9, 1995 (Box 115, Vhs 437_1065)
    - National Art Club, 1995-1996
      - Part one, March 31, 1995 (Box 99, Hi8 437_2014)
      - Part two, March 31, 1995 (Box 102, Hi8 437_2097)
      - Art Dealers, April 17, 1996 (Box 114, Vhs 437_1044)
    - Compilation Tape -- Basketball, Valentine's Day, Marble, Other Mat, February 12, 1995 (Box 144, Vhs 437_2162)
    - "City Without Walls, the Quotidian Sublime" Art Show, New Jersey, April, 1995 (Box 94, Hi8 437_1382)
    - Homage to Ray Johnson, May, 1995 (Box 94, Hi8 437_1384)
    - Lois Svard, Merkin Concert Hall, May 11, 1995 (Box 115, Vhs 437_1068)
    - "The Creative Will," Ms Grey Gallery, May 16, 1995 (Box 93, Hi8 437_1356)
    - Peter and Giorgio, Broome St. Project, October, 1995 (Box 97, Hi8 437_1969)
    - Cecil Taylor and Christine Berl, Merkin Concert Hall, October 12, 1995 (Box 124, Vhs 437_1400)
    - Merce Cunningham at Jupiter, Yoshimi, November, 1995 (Box 102, Hi8 437_2105)
    - The Roscoe Mitchell New Chamber Ensemble, Merkin Concert Hall, December 7, 1995 (Box 124, Vhs 437_1401)
    - "The Quotidian Sublime: Looking at the Overlooked" Exhibit, One Gateway Center, March 16 - April 28, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - "Digital Sites" Exhibit, @ CAFE, August 6 - September 2, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - International Sorak Biennale, August 13 - 26, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - NY SOHO Biennial, September - October, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Art Outside, 1995 (Box 94, Hi8 437_1379)
    - Artnet International, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Dance Party Tape, 1995 (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0928)
    - Joan talks for book, 1995 (Box 136, Vhs 437_1756)
    - "Nachtbogen" Performance, Berlin, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Artnet, 1995-1997
      - Artists Space, 1995 (Box 94, Hi8 437_1378)
      - Storefront for Art and Architecture, February, 1995 (Box 94, Hi8 437_1376)
      - Pseudo, March 25, 1997 (Box 135, Vhs 437_1729)
      - Performance, March 25, 1997 (Box 137, Vhs 437_1793)
      - Video, undated (Box 137, Vhs 437_1795)
    - Hedda Sterne, 1995-1997
      - Video (Box 144, Vhs 437_2145)
      - Video (Box 93, Hi8 437_1343)
    - Livig Tones, Merkin Concert Hall, circa 1995-1997 (Box 115, Vhs 437_1066)
    - T. Buckner, Merkin Concert Hall, circa 1995-1997 (Box 115, Vhs 437_1063)
    - Dahesh Museum Events, January, 1996
      - "Picturing the Middle East / A Hundred Years of Orientalism," Dahesh Museum, January, 1996 (Box 141, Vhs 437_1917)
      - "19th Century Origins of American Archeology," Terry Waltz, Dahesh Museum, January 10, 1996 (Box 143, Vhs 437_1930)
      - Video, January 10-16, 1996 (Box 93, Hi8 437_1342)
        Includes "19th Century Origins of American Archeology," Terry Walz and "At the Edge of the Sahara: Historic Synagogues in Morocco," Joel Zack
      - "The West's Fascination with the Weavings of the Middle East," Peter Davies, Dahesh Museum, January 23, 1996 (Box 93, Hi8 437_1360)
      - Ingrid Curuso Gersin, Dahesh Museum, January 27, 1996 (Box 93, Hi8 437_1352)
      - Video, January, 1996 (Box 141, Vhs 437_1916)
    - David Rosenbloom, Henry Threadgill, Merkin Concert Hall, January 11, 1996
      - Video (Box 114, Vhs 437_1038)
      - Video (Box 115, Vhs 437_1058)
    - "An Immersive Environment" Benefit Party, February 12, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - RELACHE, Merkin Concert Hall, February 29, 1996 (Box 124, Vhs 437_1399)
    - Joan La Barbara, March 7, 1996 (Box 115, Vhs 437_1070)
    - Kwok Mang Ho -- Frog Opening, Taipei Gallery, March 20, 1996
      - Video (Box 143, Vhs 437_2136)
      - Video (Box 99, Hi8 437_2009)
    - The Barton Workshop, Merkin Concert Hall, April 18, 1996 (Box 115, Vhs 437_1059)
    - Carl Stone and Far East Side Band, Merkin Concert Hall, May 2, 1996 (Box 115, Vhs 437_1061)
    - Taipei Theater, May 3, 1996
      - Part one (Box 94, Hi8 437_1389)
      - Part two (Box 99, Hi8 437_2015)
    - Squat Opening, Artists Space, May 14, 1996
      - Video (Box 98, Hi8 437_1989)
      - Video (Box 100, Hi8 437_2054)
    - James Emery and the Deep Listening Band, Merkin Concert Hall, May 30, 1996 (Box 114, Vhs 437_1051)
    - Alex Schloss Exhibit, June, 1996 (Box 101, Hi8 437_2091)
    - B.ESS, June, 1996 (Box 99, Hi8 437_2005)
    - NY presentation, Kuang Yu CTW, August 5, 1996 (Box 98, Hi8 437_1991)
    - John Gibson plays Jene Highstein at Ace, August 15, 1996 (Box 141, Vhs 437_1919)
    - Tim Druckrey -- Rotterdam, Lantern, September 22, 1996 (Box 100, Hi8 437_2044)
    - Daniel Rotham, Merkin Concert Hall, October 17, 1996 (Box 115, Vhs 437_1064)
    - Ken Hiratsuka -- "Life Line," "The Emerging Collector", November, 1996 (Box 97, Hi8 437_1965)
    - Malcolm Goldstein and Gustavo Matamoros, Merkin Concert Hall, December 4, 1996 (Box 115, Vhs 437_1069)
    - Dahesh Museum, 1996 (Box 143, Vhs 437_1926)
    - Electronic Sculptures -- A Work in Progress, 1996 (Box 144, Vhs 437_2150)
    - Marble Prototype, Harvestworks Benefit, 1996 (Box 100, Hi8 437_2043)
    - Marble Sounds, 1996 (Box 102, Hi8 437_2106)
    - Martini Beach and Westbeth, 1996 (Box 98, Hi8 437_1977)
    - Joan, 1996 (Box 99, Hi8 437_2004)
    - Jack Waters Performances and Art Samples, 1996-2005; FA_MSS_437_ER_15
    - CTW Kuang Yu Jong, Zhang Boils, The Ocean, January 31, 1997 (Box 100, Hi8 437_2041)
    - Interpretations, Harold Budd and Jon Gibson, Merkin Concert Hall, April 24, 1997 (Box 114, Vhs 437_1057)
    - Mac B/U Kong (HD), May 8, 1997 (Box 84, Dat 437_0794)
    - "Switch! A Jam Session with a Couple of Cues," Squid, May 16, 1997
      - Ephemera (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Video (Box 92, Hi8 437_1326)
    - Jon Myers, bang on a can, May 18, 1997 (Box 101, Hi8 437_2064)
    - Marbleyes, Storefront for Art and Architecture, June 20, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 15, 16, Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Paul, Gisella, Sarah, Susanna, June 20-28, 1997 (Box 92, Hi8 437_1338)
      Full label reads: "Storefront, Brooklyn w/ Paul, Gisella, Sarah, Susanna at Museum of Natural [History]"
    - Soundlab, Roosevelt Park, July, 1997 (Box 135, Vhs 437_1725)
    - Nine Dragon Heads International Environment Art Festival and Symposium, Korea, August, 1997
      - Poster and ephemera (Box 10, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
      - Video (Box 98, Hi8 437_1990)
      - Video (Box 137, Vhs 437_1797)
    - Environment and Soundlab, Roosevelt Park -- Nik and DJ Spooky, August, 1997 (Box 93, Hi8 437_1344)
    - Charlie Morrow, Shalom, Rotherham, October 2-27, 1997 (Box 91, Hi8 437_1305)
    - A's at Puffin Room, October 24-27, 1997
      - Video, October 24, 1997 (Box 94, Hi8 437_1406)
      - Video, October 24, 1997 (Box 90, Hi8 437_1255)
      - Video, October 24, 1997 (Box 128, Vhs 437_1582)
      - Video, October 25, 1997 (Box 90, Hi8 437_1257)
      - Video, October 25, 1997 (Box 143, Vhs 437_1935)
      - Carlton Bright, October 27, 1997 (Box 120, Vhs 437_1216)
    - Carlton Bright -- Eyes, Mod Style, December 18-23, 1997 (Box 88, Minidv 437_0966)
    - Carlton Bright and Arleen, December 23, 1997 (Box 141, Vhs 437_1922)
    - Shu Uemura and Arleen, December 28, 1997 (Box 88, Minidv 437_0965)
    - Brooklyn Botanic Garden, December 31, 1997 (Box 89, Minidv 437_1014)
    - "A's Revival Weekend," Loft Pioneer Show, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Chung Buck, Korea, 1997 (Box 134, U-matic 437_1693)
    - Compilation Tape -- Confession Under Luna, No Se No Demo, Unstoppable Watchable, 1997 (Box 120, Vhs 437_1211)
    - "Millenial Grooves" -- Technotox, Debra Hampton, AIR Gallery, 1997 (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0945)
      Arleen Schloss is credited as participating artist
    - Storefront, 1997 (Box 135, Vhs 437_1720)
    - Windows of Chance Performance, Pseudo Studio, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Jaz disk 3 B/U, January 10,1998 (Box 84, Dat 437_0793)
    - Arleen Poetics, January 15, 1998 (Box 96, Minidv 437_1481)
    - Hedda Sterne, CDs, February, 1998 (Box 106, Minidv 437_2301)
    - Allison Knowles, March 3, 1998 (Box 88, Minidv 437_0991)
    - Shu Uemura, April 12, 1998 (Box 115, Vhs 437_1060)
    - I Ching -- Nina, Barbara, Bettina, July 23, 1998 (Box 88, Minidv 437_0988)
    - Kathy Marsan -- Pub, International House, July 27, 1998 (Box 143, Vhs 437_1934)
    - Glenn Branca at the Knitting Factory, October 17, 1998
      - Part one (Box 89, Minidv 437_1005)
      - Part two (Box 89, Minidv 437_1004)
      - Part three (Box 89, Minidv 437_1003)
    - Hedda Sterne Exhibition, 1998 (Box 135, Vhs 437_1717)
    - Hedda Sterne at CDS, 1998 (Box 135, Vhs 437_1715)
    - Light Forms, 1998 (Box 144, Vhs 437_2159)
      NTSC
    - Arts Connection, February 27, 1999 (Box 89, Minidv 437_0997)
    - Armand Schwerner Banquet, April 11, 1999
      - Part one (Box 89, Minidv 437_1026)
      - Part two (Box 89, Minidv 437_1027)
      - Part three (Box 89, Minidv 437_1028)
    - Peking Opera Loft, May 1, 1999 (Box 88, Minidv 437_0978)
    - Construction [Company], May 6-7, 1999 (Box 88, Minidv 437_0985)
    - Bob B and Dalai Lama, The Lincoln Center, August, 1999 (Box 106, Minidv 437_2328)
    - Jaron Linier, August 19, 1999 (Box 95, Minidv 437_1425)
    - Life Cafe, November, 1999 (Box 106, Minidv 437_2340)
    - "New Year's Eve 2000.0", December 31, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Art Festival, Sweden, 1999 (Box 144, Vhs 437_2158)
    - "Hallo Alter" Installation -- Proposal, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Hedda Sterne, 1999 (Box 106, Minidv 437_2299)
    - Orchid Show, 1999 (Box 128, Vhs 437_1591)
    - The Orodox, Luk Tung Kuen, 1999 (Box 89, Minidv 437_1011)
    - Throat singing, 1999 (Box 106, Minidv 437_2336)
    - "Women of the Book: Jewish Artists, Jewish Themes" Exhibit, Gotthelf Art Gallery, 1999 - 2001 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Etoy and DJ Spooky, April, 2000 (Box 106, Minidv 437_2318)
    - Yoko, DJ, and Thursten, Battery Park, June 3, 2000; cuid41513 (Box 96, Minidv 437_1493)
      Duration: 27 minutes
    - Lincoln Center, Tibet Hotel, Cage, Dalia, August, 2000 (Box 106, Minidv 437_2313)
    - Steve Black, Exit Art, September 9, 2000 (Box 106, Minidv 437_2326)
    - Hedda Sterne, CDS, December 12, 2000 (Box 91, Minidv 437_2292)
    - Kevin and Phoebe (Dub), May 12, 2001 (Box 106, Minidv 437_2339)
    - Concert for City of New York, October 20, 2001 (Box 114, Vhs 437_1046)
    - St. Marks, January 1, 2002 (Box 96, Minidv 437_1534)
    - Remote Benefit, March, 2002 (Box 87, Minidv 437_2279)
    - Roberta Berman with Numbers, January 16, 2003 (Box 114, Vhs 437_1053)
    - "Howl! Festival of East Village Arts", August 21, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - An M Shot Chance, The Construction Company, November 16, 2003
      - Ephemera (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Video (Box 96, Minidv 437_1515)
    - Emma Sings, 2003 (Box 97, Minidv 437_1541)
    - Summer Party 2004, Tibetans 2005, 2004-2005 (Box 96, Minidv 437_1479)
    - Compilation Tape -- Union Square, Germany, September 2, 2004 (Box 135, Vhs 437_1724)
    - Plexus, December 10, 2005
      - #1 (Box 97, Minidv 437_1549)
      - #2 (Box 97, Minidv 437_1551)
      - Adil #2 (Box 97, Minidv 437_1545)
      - Elliot #1 (Box 97, Minidv 437_1544)
      - Elliot #3 (Box 97, Minidv 437_1550)
    - Joe, 2006 (Box 90, Minidv 437_2283)
    - Ken Hiratsuka Open Studio, March 25, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Jack Waters, Babette, August 19, 2007 (Box 107, Minidv 437_2352)
    - Storefront for Art and Architecture, September 21, 2007 (Box 107, Minidv 437_2350)
    - Joe Lewis, September 29, 2007 (Box 107, Minidv 437_2381)
    - Alan Vega, Storefront for Art and Architecture, October 7, 2007
      - Part one (Box 107, Minidv 437_2400)
      - Part two (Box 107, Minidv 437_2401)
    - Roberta Friedman, October 20, 2007
      - Part one (Box 107, Minidv 437_2372)
      - Part two (Box 107, Minidv 437_2373)
    - "Z-A", 2007 (Box 157, Minidv 437_1510)
    - Friends Show -- Ken Hiratsuka, February 8, 2008
      - Part one (Box 106, Minidv 437_2348)
      - Part two (Box 107, Minidv 437_2349)
    - "OP on Screen Interactive" Performance, NYPL, October 15 - 24, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - "Echolations" by Arleen Schloss and Emma Zakarevicius, NYPL, October 24, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - A and Emma, NYPL, October 29, 2009 (Box 96, Minidv 437_1514)
    - "A2Z Instant Riffs" Installation, 2012; FA_MSS_437_ER_16
    - Negative Utopia: Responses to Downtown New York Exhibit, the New Museum, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - "Speaking in Tongues" Exhibit, December 5, 2012 - January 27, 2013
      - Artist statements (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Electronic Records, FA_MSS_437_ER_17
    - & Opera Cabaret -- Proposal, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - 2+4 tracks, undated (Box 66, Audiocassette 437_0055)
    - "626 Benefit", undated (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - "A Dofferemt Doréctopm," 8 B.C., undated (Box 10, Folder 16)